rian Harminto

🛮 (+1) 626-242-0061 | 🔀 adrian.harminto@gmail.com | 🏕 kuzame.github.io | 🖸 kuzame | 🛅 adrian-h

Profile

- Proficient with debugging codes, managing version control, and deriving user requirements/demands
- Experience with software development practices, network protocols w/ over-the-air practices, and unix sysadmin

Skills

Programming Language Python, Java, C/C++, JavaScript, Bash Scripting/Shell, HTML, Swift (iOS), C#

Frameworks/Tools Terminal, Git/Github, SSH, NGINX, React, Firebase, SQL, Linux, Windows, Photoshop, ETFX, MS Offices

Work Experience

dot11labs (WiFi performance testing labs)

June 2018-Present

Riverside

SOFTWARE TEST ENGINEER

Program an automation of testing network performance and turntables written in Python to obtain router's throughput and RSSI

- Control multiple access points, stations, and turntables at the same time in the automation
- Control testing network performance SW with IxChariot, octoScope's stardust-UI supported iPerf3, or custom manual iPerf3
- Contribute to 99% of custom manual iPerf3 automation's development
- Develop DIY turntable using motion sensor & stepper motor controlled by Raspberry Pi 3B+ with motor HAT in Python

University of California, Riverside (International Affairs)

July 2018-Present

IT STUDENT ASSISTANT

Riverside

- · Set-up, implement, and perform data migration for office visa management system using Immigration Tracker
- Create a detailed user guide with tutorials for Immigration Tracker usage
- Assist with system record clean-up, data migration of records/documents
- Program a python script that accelerates finding scholars of desired criteria automatically (from ISS website)

Projects

ExSim Winter 2019

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER LEAD

- Build an Excitement Simulator application: https://exsim.github.io
- Develop the front-end UI with FXML and connect the UI controller to the simulator engine
- Develop the functions, fetchers, and parsers for both front-end and back-end

Huddle - Web REACT Application

Sept 2017 - Jan 2018

PRODUCT MANAGER/SOFTWARE DEV

- Build a software development cycle management tool: https://huddlereflex.github.io
- A web based application using Javascript's React, Firebase, NGINX & Droplet
- Work on user authentication (Login/Register), board's functionality, about & team pages.

Rotatable PIR Sensor April 2017 - June 2017

EMBEDDED SYSTEMS

• Build an embedded system of sensor that can rotate in multi direction:

http://youtu.be/GwYmqF7stqE https://github.com/Kuzame/RotatablePIR

- Application of task scheduler and PWM
- Usage of devices such as servo motor, PIR, and ultrasonic sensor w/o arduino

Fan UI Manager

September 2015 - December 2015

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER MEMBER

- Build a UI for fan manager using JavaFX (Java library): https://github.com/Kuzame/Team02
- Using arduino, enable user to control the fan's speed and detect its temperature

Education

University of California, Riverside

Expected Graduation: April 2019